Wow! I finally got you,
Tatemoto Bread's egg sandwich!
Hey, your egg's shining like gold bars.
Deliciousmile!
Ooh, your sweetness
brings happiness to me.
It's as exciting as
when I'm lying in a field
to see four-leaf clovers
surrounding me.
Yup! Posted on Curesta.
You're talking to a sandwich?
What?
Shinpei Takagi
You're weird, Hanamichi.
Delicious!
Savor the smiles
It becomes yummy
Delicious Party Pretty Cure!
(Cure Cure)
(Pretty Cure)
Melody of a rumbling tummy
Let it be in unison
Non-stop hunger
I can't wait
Eating happily and cooking with love
Together with my loved ones
Come, dig in!
A symphony of happiness
Sizzle, sizzle
Cut, cut (Hey!)
Let's party!
(Yeah!)
Gather together! Cheers!
(Cheers!)
Delicious!
Savor the smiles
I want to share
this excitement with love
Hand in hand
Even our hearts
will become stronger
As we say our thanks
It becomes yummy
Delicious Party Pretty Cure!
Ran-Ran's Weird?!
Meat Stew and a Lie.
Are you serious?
I totally am.
But it's unbelievable.
Morning!
Morning.
How are you, Yui-san?
Huh?! What's up, Ran?
She talks this way to me, too.
Ran, did anything happen?
No. Please do not worry.
"Please"?!
Oh, yeah!
I saw your egg sandwich on Curesta.
Stay!
Really? Your Curesta account
is a secret at school?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
But why?
You think...Ran-Ran's weird, right?
- What?
- Huh?
Takagi-kun saw me
praising the egg sandwich
and said I'm weird.
Really?!
Oh my...
But then, his stories are also...
It's true. Some aliens
almost abducted me yesterday.
Gosh, I bet you're lying.
Why did they target you?
Whoa.
Don't blab this to anyone.
My brother's working on a secret mission
at the U.S. space center.
Are his stories all lies?!
- Did you believe him?
- Yes.
The one about him
being chased by 1,000 dogs?
Or about his collection
of imps' plates?
I thought his life was so thrilling.
Oh, please.
It can't be.
Ran-Ran told my grade-school friends
about my favorite stuff,
such as food and many other things.
But it seemed it was too much.
Ran-chan, you're kind of weird.
Oh?!
- Wanna play on the swing?
- Yup.
And then Ran-Ran has decided
not to talk about stuff like that.
But!
But it was hard
to hide my passion for food.
We have so many delicious things.
I was keen to tell people about them.
And started posting on Curesta?
Yeah.
Thank you for listening, ladies.
- Oh?
- Ran?
Have a nice day.
I swear Hanamichi
can understand sandwich language.
You're kidding.
The sandwich told her,
"I'm sand-w-ich.
Pronounce it properly, okay?"
Takagi-kun.
What?
Don't tell a lie about Ran.
She was really talking
to a sandwich.
Huh?! Um, that may be true, but...
See? You know I'm right.
Anyway, stop talking about her weirdly.
She's worried about your word "weird."
But talking to a sandwich
is just weird, yeah?
Th...That shows
how much she likes it.
I said she was weird
when she was weird.
Any problem?
Let's go guys.
Ahh...
Oh! Hi, Ran.
Oh no...
Bundoru.
Bundoru? Bundoru.
Don't slack off.
Anyway, does he really
want a new pose?
Sir Godatz.
I heard that
someone named Black Pepper appeared.
Yes, sir.
And he has a Delicioustone too.
All the Recipeppis should belong to me.
Whoever it is,
I won't let anyone get in my way.
Narcistoru, take care of it.
Yes, sir!
Ready, let's do this.
Bundoru, Bundoru.
All right,
let's have a ramen party today!
Kome, kome!
Let's slurp noodles!
Okay, we have the recipe here.
Ramen
But!
Pipi.
Huh?
W...Whoa!
The one most familiar with ramen is...
Please give us a lesson!
Huh? What?
Ran, please.
Um...
What do we do first?
Oh, yeah. It's making a broth.
Am I right?
Stay!
First comes...dried bonito.
Oh?
Wow, Ran!
Yeah. Plus...dried sardine and kelp.
Use another pan.
Then mix it with chicken stock.
Okay, I'll use this pan...
Wait, let Ran-Ran do it.
Sure thing!
Oh, dear.
Deliciousmile!
This chicken and Japanese style broth's
perfect harmony
organizes an orchestra of food!
A perfectly symphonizing taste
is completed!
Time to eat!
Deliciousmile!
It's so yummy.
Doubly upsized craziness!
Slurp-slurp!
Slurp-slurp.
Wow, it's awesome!
Thank you, guys!
Glad you picked yourself.
Food brings smiles!
Girls, I just realized
that being weird is wonderful.
What, wonderful?
Yes, it's just that everyone has
their own favorite. That's not weird.
I'm always thinking about food.
I'm weird too.
It's wonderful
to say you like something.
Don't hesitate to say it.
Ran, the monster size
of your passion for food is a gift!
No matter who says what,
you can be confident.
Because you like it so much.
Ooh!
That's right.
I like your personality very much, Ran.
Me too.
I like listening to your story.
I like it too.
- Mem!
- Pam!
Thank you.
Ran-Ran is getting confident.
Won't be worried
about Takagi-kun anymore.
Talking about something fun?
Hey, Mom.
Kome!
Did someone say Takagi-kun earlier?
Huh? Yeah.
Take our diner's lunch box
to him tomorrow.
How come?
Just now, I met his mother by chance.
You know, his parents manage a store.
So his brother had taken care of him.
But he left home for a distant college.
Huh? Isn't Takagi-kun's brother
in America?
America?
For a job related to space programs...
Is that also a lie?
Ah, he said he wanted to study
that field to work in America.
Sounds great.
So, Takagi-kun is alone at home?
Seems like it.
I heard that his brother
prepared meals for him before.
So, give it to him tomorrow.
The words space and his brother
were true.
I guess he feels lonely.
He suddenly became alone
due to his brother's college.
I see.
I'm tired...
Were you guys hiding?
Sweet dreams.
Oh, that's Takagi-kun.
Sankai Dining
Meat Stew
Whoa, meat stew!
Pipi.
Recipeppi!
That looks tasty...hmm?
Oh? It seems something
about Takagi-kun is bothering Ran.
Toru-run, Toru-run, Bundoru!
Pipi!
Pipi.
Narcistoru, return the Recipeppi!
It's just one of them.
Just one of them to you may be
someone else's precious one!
Why did I want to eat meat stew?
I feel like I have a cherished memory...
Ran!
Hey!
Guys!
Come on, Motto Ubau-zo!
Motto Ubau-zo!
Delicious Field!
Let's go, guys!
Okay!
Pretty Cure, Delicious stand-by,
Party, Go!
Squeeze!
Kome Kome!
From the heart!
Open!
Pam Pam!
Sandwich!
Round and round!
Mem Mem!
With a Miracle!
Sharin' Energy!
Kome!
Tasty!
Wonton!
Kome Kome!
Pam Pam!
Mem Mem!
Brimming with energy,
from piping-hot rice!
Cure Precious!
I'll fill you up with a delicious smile!
With a dainty sandwich,
spice for your heart!
Cure Spicy!
You won't forget this shared tastiness!
Sparkling noodle emotion!
Cure Yum-Yum!
I won't let you hog all the good stuff!
Delicious Party Pretty Cure!
Motto Ubau-zo.
Girls!
It's...crushing us.
What should we do?
Oh, no!
Takagi-kun's face showed he has
a precious memory of meat stew.
No one shouldn't
steal such memories from others.
Definitely!
Ultra Crunchy Cutter Blades!
How reckless.
It's not reckless!
Yes!
Gosh!
Nice job!
Ultra Crunchy Cutter Blades!
Thanks!
Precious, now!
My chance!
1000 Kilocalorie Punch!
Zo!
Nice! Now Yum-Yum,
give it a giga-sized one to finish!
All right!
Cure Yum-Yum, Heart Juicy Mixer!
Sharin'!
Energy!
Mix!
Mem!
Pretty Cure! Delicious Yum-Yum Drain!
I'm stuffed!
That was delicious!
Pipi!
Welcome back.
I don't chase those who leave.
What was that?
Ran-Ran is going in.
What?
Hey, may I try a bit?
Oh, Hanamichi?
Um...sure.
Thanks.
It's so yummy.
Social dancing
between meat and potatoes.
Shall we dance?
Huh? What do you mean?
I mean, it's super tasty.
But you looked sad
when you ate it earlier. Why?
Wait, you were watching?
Don't be so nosey.
I'm asking you on behalf of meat stew.
Sorry?
Give me a clear reason.
Um... This meat stew
isn't as sweet as I expected.
Hmm?
My brother's meat stew
was always sweet.
I expected the same one here.
It tastes good but not sweet enough.
Hmm... I see.
Got it.
The answer is onion.
Onion?
I think your brother took much time
to sauté onions until brown
and put them in his meat stew.
Right, he always
took a long time to make it.
That must be the secret
of his sweet meat stew.
Yay, the case is closed!
How do you know things like that?
That's beacause
Ran-Ran likes food so much.
Okay then, see you!
You're really weird.
You surely are,
but maybe you're cool too.
Here.
Wow.
What's this?
It's based on
Takagi-kun's brother's special recipe.
A meat stew lunch.
Yui-pyon's mother made it for you.
And Ran created the recipe.
Oh, look at this!
So?
Oh, gosh!
How sweet and delicious!
It looks really yummy.
I'm a cyborg
powered by tasty meat stew!
You are?!
I heard that his brother
always laughed at his stories.
That's why?
Yup.
- Just one bite, please.
- No, it's mine.
Today's strawberry juice.
Cheers!
Time for a delicious smile at full power
Let's dig into this merry day
So happy! So fun!
A large serving of happy days
Don't hold back, get your fill
Let's begin this delicious party!
Delicious memories make my heart
soft and warm with glee
I'd love to share such days with you
Hungry friends, gather around
Hello to food
made with tender loving care
Once we're on standby, hands together
Gulp, give thanks
to this dish full of love
Time for a delicious smile at full power
Let's play with everyone in high spirits
So happy! So fun!
Taste this precious time
A toast to that sparkling smile
Let's enjoy with a warm heart
Come join our delicious party!
- What?!
- Amane-san will...
- Quit her...
- President's post?
She may be dwelling
on her past as Gentlu.
Let's go see her.
Okay!
Delicious Party Pretty Cure.
The Fourth Pretty Cure?!
Amane's Choice.